

About Me

I'm a developer turned designer. Ever since I can remember, I've had a passion for design. While doing frontend programming for two years, I couldn't contain my desire to design what I was developing so I decided to pursue my true passion.

Experience

UserTesting

Frontend Engineer Intern | May 2016 - Sept 2016

I helped centralized design components across the UserTesting product. Working with designers and frontend enginers, I designed and developed an asset toolkit, which was a style guide for developers to reference when coding components.

Flawless Repairs

Frontend Engineer Intern | May 2016 - Sept 2016

Starting from scratch, I created a brand identity and designed and developed a website for Flawless Repairs which followed similar patterns of IT repair websites.

Projects

Morgan State University: HBCU Hackathon

Android Application Developer | Jan 2016

In 24 hours, I was able to create QuickGift, an app that helps people find a gift for someone special in their life, based on gender, relationship, and occausion. I won second place at the competition.

AdsNative Hackathon

Ul Designer | Jun 2016

I worked as my team's UI designer, researching problems with Spotify's current ad implementation. From there, i redesigned the ad experience to be more targeted and less intrusive to the user. My team won second place.

Education

Capitol Technology University

Computer Science major | Aug 2013 - Dec 2017

I have a 3.2 GPA. I am president of the National Society of Black Engineers (NSBE), treasurer of Student Government Association, and a member of the Student Ambassador program.

Skills

